Justina, I realize that Elaine's death must have been shocking for you, but don't you think that arresting Calence was a bit extreme?
I understand. I'm prepared to face the consequences, Mistress, no matter what you decide. However...
What is it?
I thought that if I didn't do something, then they'd never reveal the reason they were there. But perhaps Calence will confide in you, great priestess.
I've heard that Mistress Elaine was practically immortal.
I doubt that the tears of blood would have had the power to kill her.
It's more likely that they were set up.
But Calence didn't say anything, except that he'd accept whatever decision we make, and we can't hold him captive based on that.
Like you said, there's probably some other explanation.
Justina, go with the tears of blood and watch over him.
Calence is like a son to me, so try and keep him out of harm's way, as you would with a graene.
I understand.
Mistress Lydren?